artprize.org 2010-06-20

# ArtPrize - An open art contest based in Grand Rapids Michigan, the world's largest Art Prize.

**EFFECTIVE DATE:** April 4th, 2009

ArtPrize Grand Rapids ("ArtPrize") values the privacy of its web site visitors and hopes that the following statement helps you understand how ArtPrize collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide us through our web site, artprize.org and its pages (" **Site** "):

  * When you visit the Site, ArtPrize collects personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is information that is not otherwise publicly available, and may include such things as your first and last name, e-mail address, zip code, image, username and password, and other information that you provide to us. Do not submit information that you do not want ArtPrize to access. ArtPrize may use personally identifiable information to provide information and services to Site users and to allow ArtPrize to (i) respond to user questions and comments, (ii) analyze and monitor consumer and customer activity, (iii) promote and support ArtPrize products and services, (iv) develop a knowledge base regarding its Site users; and (v) verify the authenticity of votes or other information received in connection with ArtPrize. ArtPrize may disclose personally identifiable information in response to law enforcement activity, to enforce its contracts or property rights, or when required by law. Information collected may also be transferred in connection with the sale or merger of the company or any division or business line of the company to which the information relates. If ArtPrize hires any third parties to perform services relating to the way the Site functions, it will require them to protect your personally identifiable information in the same way that ArtPrize does.

  1.     * In addition to the disclosures set forth above, ArtPrize may aggregate personally identifiable information about its users and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties (including advertisers) for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. In those cases, the third parties will not be able to identify any individual user of the Site based on the disclosures.
  2.     * ArtPrize may also use different technologies, such as cookies, to passively collect information. The information collected might include the date and time you visit the Site, logs from your browser, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and the pages you requested. This information will usually be used to (i) customize the advertising and content you see, (ii) process and confirm your entries and votes for our contest, (iii) contact you, and (iv) enhance your experience. Your browser must be set up to accept cookies in order to fully utilize certain areas of the Site.
  3.     * ArtPrize intends to use commercially reasonable means to protect the integrity of its Site and the confidentiality of the personally identifiable information that you provide. While ArtPrize considers online security a priority, it cannot provide absolute assurances against, and will not be liable for, any breaches of confidentiality due to system failures or unauthorized access by third parties.
  4.     * ArtPrize intends this Site for use only by individuals who are 18 years of age or older. Although you may vote in a contest if you are 16 years of age or older, please do not use the Site without the permission and involvement of a parent or guardian if you are not at least 18 years of age.
  5.     * ArtPrize reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. When material changes have been made to this Privacy Policy, ArtPrize will indicate this fact on the Site with a link to the revised version of the Privacy Policy. Any material change to this Privacy Policy will also be indicated on the main page of our Site with a link to the revised Privacy Policy. Please check the Privacy Policy regularly to review the changes.
  6. If you do provide ArtPrize with personally identifiable information, then you may opt out of additional uses of your personally identifiable information. To opt out, email [support@artprize.org](mailto:support@artprize.org)

  7. Questions regarding the Site or this Privacy Policy should be sent to [support@artprize.org](mailto:support@artprize.org)
